<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- 
 * Funf: Open Sensing Framework
 * Copyright (C) 2010-2011 Nadav Aharony, Wei Pan, Alex Pentland. 
 * Acknowledgments: Alan Gardner
 * Contact: nadav@media.mit.edu
 * 
 * This file is part of Funf.
 * 
 * Funf is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
 * it under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public License as 
 * published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of 
 * the License, or (at your option) any later version. 
 * 
 * Funf is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but 
 * WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of 
 * MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  
 * See the GNU Lesser General Public License for more details.
 * 
 * You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public 
 * License along with Funf. If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
 -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ACTIVITY_ENTRY_NAME</string>
    <string name="app_ver">v0.3.2.2</string>
    <string name="app_id">355198514515820</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>

    <string name="cancelled">Cancelled</string>
    <string name="permission_not_granted">Unable to perform selected action because permissions were not granted.</string>
    <string name="hello_user">Hello %1$s!</string>
    <string name="success">Success</string>
    <string name="successfully_posted_post">Success!</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="status_update">(DK)I am now %1$s in the SensibleDTU EpiGame!</string>
    <string name="exception">Exception: %1$s</string>


    <string name="welcome_text_1">(DK)You will take part in an interactive game study. The study consists of 12 rounds, each lasting one week. In each week, you may contract a hypothetical disease and become infectious for other participants. You can decide either for or against vaccination. You will receive 100 points in each round and may lose between 0 and 90 points in each round, depending on your decision and the decisions of other participants. At the end of the 12 weeks, there will be a lottery in that we raffle ??. The more points you have left at the end of the 12 weeks, the higher is your likelihood of winning a price in the lottery. Additionally, all participants with data quality better than 80% will receive movie vouchers every 2 weeks. </string>

    <string name="welcome_text_2">(DK)In each round, you can contract the disease. If you decide to vaccinate the vaccine becomes effective after 2 hours. Depending on your decision, you can be in one of three stages:
        1. Susceptible: You either did not vaccinate or you vaccinated within the last 2 hours, so the vaccine is not effective yet. You can contract the disease.\n
        2. Vaccinated: You vaccinated more than 2 hours ago and cannot contract the disease.\n
        3. Infected: You contracted the disease. You can infect others.
</string>

    <string name="welcome_text_3">(DK)At the beginning of each round you may randomly become sick (independent of your contacts with others) and become an infection seed.
During the game, you can contract the disease by being in physical proximity with other persons who are infected. Only susceptible people can contract the disease. The probability of contracting the disease depends on the number of other participants who are vaccinated. The greater the number of vaccinated people, the lower the probability of contracting the disease (see the next screen). If you contract the disease, you will lose between 0 and 90 points, with an average loss of 50 points. Small losses are more likely than large losses, just like mild courses of disease are more likely than severe ones. If you are infected, you can infect other susceptible participants.
</string>
    <string name="welcome_text_4"></string>
    <string name="welcome_text_5">(DK)At any time, you can vaccinate against the disease. Vaccination costs a fixed amount of 10 points. Once vaccinated, the vaccine becomes effective after 2 hours and your can no longer contract the disease. The probability of side effects due to vaccination is 30%. In case of side effects, you will lose between 0 and 90 points, with an average loss of 30 points. Small losses are more likely than large losses, just like mild side effects are more likely than severe ones. If you are vaccinated, you cannot infect others.
You can vaccinate at any time by opening the app. Additionally, you can check your current status - susceptible, vaccinated, or infected - in the app at any time.  At the end of each round, you will learn about your points earned.
</string>

    <string name="welcome_text_extra_after_wave_4">(DK)You will also receive feedback each day about the relative number of other persons you had bluetooth contact during this round, who chose to vaccinate.</string>
    <string name="welcome_text_extra_after_wave_8">(DK)You will also receive feedback each day about the relative number of all other persons playing the game, who chose to vaccinate.</string>


    <string name="vaccination_text">(DK)Vaccination costs 10 points. It prevents from contracting the disease from 2 hours after pressing the button until the end of the round. Additional point losses due to side effects might appear.</string>
    <string name="vaccination_text_disabled">(DK)You already made a vaccination decisions, please come back later...</string>
    <string name="vaccination_text_waiting">(DK)Applying vaccination...</string>

    <string name="wave_description_1">(DK)The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_2">(DK)The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_3">(DK)The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_4">(DK)The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_5">(DK)The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round, except for the fact that each day you will receive feedback about the number of infections, vaccine uptake and side effects among the participants you had bluetooth contact with. Additionally, you will learn about the resulting average probability of infection during that day.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_6">(DK)The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_7">(DK)The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_8">(DK)The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_9">(DK)The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round, except for the fact that each day you will receive feedback about the number of infections, vaccine uptake and side effects in the whole population of participants. Additionally, you will learn about the resulting average probability of infection during that day.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_10">(DK)The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_11">(DK)The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_12">(DK)The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round.</string>

    <string name="final_dialog">(DK)The competition has ended. Check out the results and prizes.</string>

    <string name="got_it">(DK)Got it!</string>
    <string name="proceed">(DK)Proceed</string>

    <string name="digest_4_intro">(DK)Yesterday (%1$s) among people you interacted with:</string>
    <string name="digest_8_intro">(DK)Yesterday (%1$s) in the global population:</string>


    <string name="digest_vaccinated_people">(DK)%1$s of vaccinated people</string>
    <string name="digest_side_people">(DK)%1$s of vaccinated people with side effects</string>
    <string name="digest_infected_people">(DK)%1$s of infected people</string>
    <string name="digest_susceptible_people">(DK)%1$s of susceptible people</string>

    <string name="state_susceptible">(DK)susceptible</string>
    <string name="state_infected">(DK)infected</string>
    <string name="state_vaccinated">(DK)vaccinated</string>
    <string name="state_awaiting">(DK)waiting for vaccination to become effective</string>
    <string name="state_recovered">(DK)recovered</string>

    <string name="lost_points">(DK)Because of this I lost %1$s points!</string>
    <string name="you_are">(DK)You are %1$s.</string>
    <string name="until_vaccination">(DK)minutes until vaccination is effective.</string>
    <string name="you_lost_points">(DK)And you lost %1$s points.</string>
    <string name="finished_round_as">(DK)You finished the round as</string>

    <string name="summary_header">(DK)Points you have earned this round:</string>
    <string name="summary_endowment">(DK)Endowment:</string>
    <string name="summary_fixed">(DK)Fixed costs for vaccination:</string>
    <string name="summary_infection">(DK)Points lost due to infection:</string>
    <string name="summary_side">(DK)Points lost due to side effects:</string>
    <string name="summary_earned">(DK)Points earned:</string>

    <string name="button_experiment_desc">(DK)Read experiment description</string>
    <string name="upload_on_time">(DK)Upload your data on time to get more accurate feedback.</string>
    <string name="button_share_this">(DK)Share this on Facebook</string>
    <string name="button_back">&lt;&lt; (DK)Back</string>

    <string name="toast_text">(DK)SensibleDTU EpiGame: You are %1$s and lost %2$s points!</string>


</resources>
