<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- 
 * Funf: Open Sensing Framework
 * Copyright (C) 2010-2011 Nadav Aharony, Wei Pan, Alex Pentland. 
 * Acknowledgments: Alan Gardner
 * Contact: nadav@media.mit.edu
 * 
 * This file is part of Funf.
 * 
 * Funf is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
 * it under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public License as 
 * published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of 
 * the License, or (at your option) any later version. 
 * 
 * Funf is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but 
 * WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of 
 * MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  
 * See the GNU Lesser General Public License for more details.
 * 
 * You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public 
 * License along with Funf. If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
 -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ACTIVITY_ENTRY_NAME</string>
    <string name="app_ver">v0.3.2.2</string>

    <string name="cancelled">Cancelled</string>
    <string name="permission_not_granted">Unable to perform selected action because permissions were not granted.</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="hello_user">Hello %1$s!</string>
    <string name="success">Success</string>
    <string name="successfully_posted_post">Success!</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="status_update">I am now %1$s in the SensibleDTU EpiGame!</string>
    <string name="app_id">355198514515820</string>
    <string name="exception">Exception: %1$s</string>

    <string name="welcome_text_1">You will take part in an interactive study.\n\nThe study consists of 12 rounds, each taking one week.
        You will receive 100 points in each round and may lose between 0 and 90 points in each round, depending on your decision and the decisions of other participants.\n\nAt the end of the experiment, there will be lottery in that we raffle ??.
        The more points you have at the end of the experiment, the more like you will win in the lottery.\n\nPlease click “Proceed” to receive detailed information about the study.</string>

    <string name="welcome_text_2">In each week, you may contract a hypothetical disease.\n\nYou can decide either for or against a vaccination. The vaccine becomes effective only after 2 hours after you have vaccinated.\n\nDepending on your decision, you can be in one of three states:\n
        1. Susceptible: You either did not vaccinate or vaccinated within the last 2 hours, so the vaccine is not effective yet. You may be contracting the disease.\n
        2. Vaccinated: You vaccinated at least 2 hours before and cannot contract the disease.\n
        3. Infected: You did not vaccinate and contracted the disease. You may infect others.\n\nPlease click Proceed to learn about the potential consequences of non-vaccination.
</string>

    <string name="welcome_text_3">If you do not vaccinate, you are susceptible and can fall sick with a probability of ??% (independent of your contact with others) or contract the disease by being in bluetooth contact with other persons who are infected. Only unvaccinated people can contract the disease. The probability of contracting the disease depends on the number of other participants who are vaccinated. The greater the number of vaccinated people, the lower the probability of contracting the disease for unvaccinated persons (see below).
</string>
    <string name="welcome_text_4"></string>
    <string name="welcome_text_5">In each round, you can vaccinate against the disease. Vaccination costs a fixed amount of ?? points. Once vaccinated, the vaccine becomes effective after ?? hours and your can no longer contract the disease. The probability of side effects due to vaccination is ??%. In case of side effects, you will lose between ?? and ?? points, with an average loss of ?? points. If you are vaccinated, you also cannot infect others.

In each round, you are asked once a day whether you want to vaccinate or not, until you either contracted the disease or vaccinated. However, you may vaccinate all the time by opening the app. Additionally, you can see your current state - susceptible, vaccinated, or infected - all the time in the app.  At the end of the round, you will learn about the points earned.
</string>

    <string name="welcome_text_extra_after_wave_4">You will also receive feedback each day about the relative number of other persons you had bluetooth contact during this round, who chose to vaccinate.</string>
    <string name="welcome_text_extra_after_wave_8">You will also receive feedback each day about the relative number of all other persons playing the game, who chose to vaccinate.</string>


    <string name="vaccination_text">Vaccination costs 10 points. It prevents from contracting the disease from 2 hours after pressing the button until the end of the round. Additional point losses due to side effects might appear.</string>
    <string name="vaccination_text_disabled">You already made a vaccination decisions, please come back later...</string>
    <string name="vaccination_text_waiting">Applying vaccination...</string>

    <string name="wave_description_1">The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round.\n\nClick “Proceed” to start with the new round.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_2">The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round.\n\nClick “Proceed” to start with the new round.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_3">The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round.\n\nClick “Proceed” to start with the new round.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_4">The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round.\n\nClick “Proceed” to start with the new round.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_5">The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round, except for the fact that each day you will receive feedback about the vaccine uptake among the participants you had bluetooth contact with. Additionally, you will learn about the resulting average probability of infection in the past days since the round started. </string>
    <string name="wave_description_6">The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round, except for the fact that each day you will receive feedback about the vaccine uptake among the participants you had bluetooth contact with. Additionally, you will learn about the resulting average probability of infection in the past days since the round started. </string>
    <string name="wave_description_7">The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round, except for the fact that each day you will receive feedback about the vaccine uptake among the participants you had bluetooth contact with. Additionally, you will learn about the resulting average probability of infection in the past days since the round started. </string>
    <string name="wave_description_8">The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round, except for the fact that each day you will receive feedback about the vaccine uptake among the participants you had bluetooth contact with. Additionally, you will learn about the resulting average probability of infection in the past days since the round started. </string>
    <string name="wave_description_9">The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round, except for the fact that each day you will receive feedback about the vaccine uptake in the whole population of participants. Additionally, you will learn about the resulting average probability of infection in the past days since the round started.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_10">The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round, except for the fact that each day you will receive feedback about the vaccine uptake in the whole population of participants. Additionally, you will learn about the resulting average probability of infection in the past days since the round started.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_11">The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round, except for the fact that each day you will receive feedback about the vaccine uptake in the whole population of participants. Additionally, you will learn about the resulting average probability of infection in the past days since the round started.</string>
    <string name="wave_description_12">The next round starts now. The rules are the same as in the previous round, except for the fact that each day you will receive feedback about the vaccine uptake in the whole population of participants. Additionally, you will learn about the resulting average probability of infection in the past days since the round started.</string>
</resources>
