<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- 
 * Funf: Open Sensing Framework
 * Copyright (C) 2010-2011 Nadav Aharony, Wei Pan, Alex Pentland. 
 * Acknowledgments: Alan Gardner
 * Contact: nadav@media.mit.edu
 * 
 * This file is part of Funf.
 * 
 * Funf is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
 * it under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public License as 
 * published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of 
 * the License, or (at your option) any later version. 
 * 
 * Funf is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but 
 * WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of 
 * MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  
 * See the GNU Lesser General Public License for more details.
 * 
 * You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public 
 * License along with Funf. If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
 -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ACTIVITY_ENTRY_NAME</string>
    <string name="app_ver">v0.3.2.2</string>

    <string name="cancelled">Cancelled</string>
    <string name="permission_not_granted">Unable to perform selected action because permissions were not granted.</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="hello_user">Hello %1$s!</string>
    <string name="success">Success</string>
    <string name="successfully_posted_post">Success!</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="status_update">I am now %1$s in the SensibleDTU EpiGame!</string>
    <string name="app_id">355198514515820</string>
    <string name="exception">Exception: %1$s</string>

    <string name="welcome_text_1">You will take part in an interactive study.\nThe study consists of 12 rounds, each taking one week. You will receive 100 points in each round and may lose between 0 and ?? points in each round, depending on your decision and the decisions of other participants. At the end of the experiment, there will be lottery in that we raffle ??. The more points you have at the end of the experiment, the more like you will win in the lottery.\nPlease click “Proceed” to receive detailed information about the study.</string>
    <string name="welcome_text_2">In each week, you may contract a hypothetical disease. You can decide either for or against a vaccination. The vaccine becomes effective only after ?? hours after you have vaccinated.\nDepending on your decision, you can be in one of three stages:\n
    1. Susceptible: You either did not vaccinate or vaccinated within the last ?? hours, so the vaccine is not effective yet. You may be contracting the disease.\n
    2. Vaccinated: You vaccinated at least ?? hours before and cannot contract the disease.\n
    3. Infected: You did not vaccinate and contracted the disease. You may infect others.\n

    Please click Proceed to learn about the potential consequences of non-vaccination.
</string>

    <string name="vaccination_text">Vaccination costs 10 points. It prevents from contracting the disease from 2 hours after pressing the button until the end of the round. Additional point losses due to side effects might appear.</string>
    <string name="vaccination_text_disabled">You already made a vaccination decisions, please come back later...</string>
    <string name="vaccination_text_waiting">Applying vaccination...</string>

    <string name="wave_description_generic">Generic wave description</string>
    <string name="wave_description_1">Wave description 1</string>


</resources>
